CONTACT

(608) 320 5876

www.kimcordova.com

Atlanta, GA - relocating to Chicago, IL

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE: BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

University of Wisconsin-Platteville

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS: THEATRE

University of Wisconsin-Platteville

GENERAL ASSEMBLY COURSES

Front-End Web Development JavaScript Development Product Management

COMPUTER SKILLS

Salesforce
Google Tools
Mac OS X & Windows OS
Looker
HTML5, CSS, JQuery
Microsoft Office & Excel
Jira, Confluence, Atlassian

KIM CORDOVA

ABOUT

Sales-trained relationship builder with 6+ years of experience in translating best practices and product knowledge into business results. I am constantly looking at the world through the lens of "how and why." An inbox-zero hero. Always the go-to person for providing support and strategic guidance when it comes to understanding and breaking down processes and complex ideas.

EXPERIENCE

SALES OPERATIONS LEAD

General Assembly | 2015 - Present

Strategize sales plans, monitor progress, and teach the skills local sales team needs to conquer aggressive quotas.

Responsible for local sales enablement strategy, planning, execution, forecasting and pipeline management.

Contribute to the global sales strategy by planning and implementing national revenue-boosting initiatives in an effort to boost company profitability.

Manage an individual quarterly pipeline of 500+ students resulting in \$300,000+ in quarterly revenue; contributed over \$2.5 million in revenue for company to date.

The work I do as the Operations Lead enables our sales team to focus on selling and relationship building by addressing operational activities such as cross-department collaboration across teams, project coordination, issue resolution, and reporting analysis to keep the sales cycle flowing.

ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE

Entercom Communications | 2014-2015

Created and actualized effective, customized marketing campaigns on three awardwinning local radio stations.

Developed relationships with new small and medium business partners and presented customized solutions to meet prospective client's marketing goals using value-based and consultative selling.

OPERATIONS PROGRAM ASSOCIATE

State of Wisconsin- Department of Health & Family Services | 2013-2014

Managed department web pages ensuring content was current, accurate, and reliable. Provided administrative support for bureau by recording and distributing meeting minutes to state-wide hospital partners and by creating presentations.

RESOURCE SUPPORT SPECIALIST

Widen Enterprises | 2013

Qualified leads from small to medium-sized technology firms to generate new long-term clients for Digital Asset Management SaaS product.

Constructed customized sales presentations for prospective clients based on understanding of their needs and technical requirements.

Performed industry research to grow sales department's understanding of prospective client base and gained valuable insight into increasingly competitive landscape.